Imagine you're a sales manager at Parch and Posey,
تخيل أنك مدير مبيعات في Parch and Posey،
and you want to see how several key accounts are performing.
وترغب في معرفة كيفية أداء العديد من الحسابات الرئيسية.
The IN function will allow you to filter data based on several possible values.
ستتيح لك دالة IN بتصفية البيانات استنادًا إلى عدة قيم محتملة.
So, if you only want to see information for
لذلك، إذا كنت تريد فقط الاطلاع على معلومات
the Walmart and Apple accounts, here's how you do it.
لحسابات Walmart وApple، فإليك الطريقة التي تفعل بها ذلك.
As with comparison operators,
كما هو الحال مع عوامل تشغيل المقارنة،
IN requires single quotation marks around
تتطلب دالة IN علامات اقتباس مفردة حول
non-numerical data while numerical data can be entered directly.
البيانات غير الرقمية في حين يمكن إدخال البيانات الرقمية مباشرة.
Let's look at the actual orders associated with those accounts.
دعونا ننظر في الطلبات الفعلية المرتبطة بهذه الحسابات.
First, make note of the account IDs here,
أولًا، دوّن معرفات الحساب هنا،
1001 for Walmart and 1021 for Apple.
1001 لـ Walmart و1021 لـ Apple.
Now we see all of the individual orders that come up for accounts 1001 and 1021,
الآن نرى جميع الطلبات الفردية التي تظهر للحسابات 1001 و1021،
and as you can see, they're all jumbled together
وكما ترى، فكلها متخبطة معًا
because there is no ORDER BY clause in the query.
لعدم وجود عبارة ORDER BY في الاستعلام.
One thing to note here is the comma between these two values.
هناك شيء واحد نلاحظه هنا، وهو الفاصلة بين هاتين القيمتين.
You can put as many values as you want inside these parentheses,
يمكنك وضع العديد من القيم التي تريدها داخل هذه الأقواس،
but you have to put a comma in between each pair of distinct values.
ولكن يجب عليك وضع فاصلة بين كل زوج من القيم المميزة.